{"question":"1800 : 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 700 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2800", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7200 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"900", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3000 * 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"27", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.03 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 70 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"560", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"21000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.42", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.036", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48000 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"100", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.8 : 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"60", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.036", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.8 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6000 : 1000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 : 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.032 : 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 * 90 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"180", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"28 : 4000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.003 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.008 : 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 800 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"48000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.2 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00015 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.24 : 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"54000 : 9000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5.4 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"300 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"600", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.054", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.4 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1600", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00027 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00035", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"60", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.018 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0035 : 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4.5 : 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"49000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"25 : 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.003 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.056", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"560", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.014 : 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.54 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5.4 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"600", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.42 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.48", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 : 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.27", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4.9 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 * 70 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.024 : 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 : 60 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.14 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"700 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.072 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.03 * 50 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1200 : 600 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.1 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.6 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"700 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4.8 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.054 : 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"300 : 300 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.045 : 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0035 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.1 : 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 90 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"270", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.021 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.3 * 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.16 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.1 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7200 : 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"400 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"200", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.6 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00018 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.09", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.012 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.014 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7.2 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.032 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.48 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 8000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"56000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.4 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4000 * 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"700 * 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00024", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 700 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4900", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.012 : 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.1 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0018", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.09", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 1000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.035", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"300 : 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 : 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.4 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5.4 : 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.1 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.54", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"600 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4800", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 : 800 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"270", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00072", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 6000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"360", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.12 : 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0042", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 700 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2100", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10 : 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 : 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20000 : 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2100 : 300 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"600 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.025 : 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"63000 : 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.4 : 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 * 9000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 : 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"80", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.1 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.56", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.042", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.01 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 : 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.014 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.042", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 2000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0014 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 90 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"540", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27 : 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.32 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200 : 40 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9000 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"36000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10 : 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6000 : 1000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00049", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.036 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.035", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"280 : 40 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.21", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.001 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.032 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 70 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"350", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"720", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.008 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.3 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"400 * 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"28", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"100", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 800 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5600", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 70 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"490", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"240 : 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.01 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.36 : 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 50 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"250", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.56 : 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.063 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 : 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40000 : 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.45 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.05", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160 : 40 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.4 : 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"800", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.24 : 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"210000 : 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3.2 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.6 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.12 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0018 : 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 9000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.042", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 : 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3000 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"500", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 70 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"560", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.16 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 * 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"720 : 90 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 * 4000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"360", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 : 100 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.3 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.48 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00016 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 600 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1200", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.4 : 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"21000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 1000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"450000 : 9000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"50", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0007 : 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 200 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1200", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 70 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"210", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5000 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0024", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.32", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.072 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.48 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0056", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0036", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 800 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"800", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3.5 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 20 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1200", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"20", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.063", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.25 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.049", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 : 300 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3500", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.03 * 4000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"120", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.001 : 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3000 : 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.6 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.01 * 200 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"210", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.6 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.01 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16 : 2000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.2 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 : 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.3 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.024", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"560 : 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.045 : 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 : 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.54 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.018 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48000 : 8000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 50 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"150", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 1000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3500", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 : 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.1 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.042", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 : 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.05", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 : 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.07", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0016 : 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.012 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7.2 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"560", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6000 * 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"240", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.18 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"80", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.4 : 70 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.03 : 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.036", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.6 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 : 800 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.07", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.48 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.081 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.024 : 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00012", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 : 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3.2 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 200 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1600", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18000 : 6000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.8 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.42", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 200 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"800", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 600 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1200", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.4 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 * 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0081", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4.2 : 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"700", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.025 : 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 200 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"200", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.3 * 200 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"60", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.32", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.1 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.2 : 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.8 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 : 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.012", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"500", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.12 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.072 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.015", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.018 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.45", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.021 : 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 60 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.008 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00016", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.1 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"180 : 30 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.4 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.63 : 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.4 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.045", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35000 : 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"14000 : 2000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.28", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.054", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6.3 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4.2 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 700 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 8000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.12 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"360 : 600 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18000 : 9000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.14 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"240", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 : 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1200 : 300 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"300 * 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"100", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"64 : 800 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 40 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0054", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.4 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"600 : 300 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 40 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.072 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4000 * 20 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"80000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.072 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.81 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1000 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"80", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.032", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30 : 1000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.035", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.024 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.8 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00045 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7000 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 20 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"60", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.003 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.021 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.3 * 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.24", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 1000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.081 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.036 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"24000 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.014 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"70", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.12 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.1 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0064 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.8 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4000 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 50 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7.2 : 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.2 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.028", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.049", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.021", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.48", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1000 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"600", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 : 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27000 : 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6000 : 6000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0064", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3.5 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 * 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.021", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4.8 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"400 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.56", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.32 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.018 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"800 * 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0035 : 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 : 2000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8.1 : 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 : 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.54 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.6 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.27", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.001 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.012 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.001 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 9000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"54000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7200", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.63", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.3 * 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0027", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.014 : 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.63 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.054", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.024 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"240 : 60 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"60", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7.2 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.01 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.05", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"48000 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6.4 : 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00028", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2800 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.2 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1800", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.025 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.05", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.32", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"900 : 100 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 4000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"280", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.035", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 400 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00054 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 : 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00016 : 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 : 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.6 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"60", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 600 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"600", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.048", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1500 : 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 : 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 : 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"450", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16000 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5400 : 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"480", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.2 : 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27000 : 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.048 : 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.032 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.2 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00072 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"720 : 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.36 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.63 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.07", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.5 : 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3200 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.018", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.054 : 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.048 : 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.012 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.18 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0016", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"320 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"80", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3200 : 800 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.24 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"120", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.063", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 : 10 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 8000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"24000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"640 : 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"150", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.027 : 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.4 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2000 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4500 : 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"900", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1000 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 : 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.1 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9000 * 50 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"450000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6300 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"700", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 30 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"270", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0006 : 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3.5 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.054 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 * 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.54 : 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.63 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45000 : 9000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.64", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0012 : 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.15", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 : 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 * 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00014", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 * 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.3 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 * 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.72", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 9000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"54000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"12000 : 6000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.27 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.032", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 100 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"200", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0008 : 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7000 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1800", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4000 : 4000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 : 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 * 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00054", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.042", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.4 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.045 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.003 : 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00032", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.054", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"240", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.048", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.63 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.09", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"45000 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.18", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.48 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0048 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.003 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.2 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.05", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00012 : 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.024 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.4 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1400 : 200 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7000 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"14000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"360 : 90 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4000 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 : 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"100", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.072", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.012", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.6 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.32 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.08", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3000 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"12000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.042 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.003 : 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 * 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.00045", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"72 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.03 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.027 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"50 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"150", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 : 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0012", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.2 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"12000 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.015 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.008 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"80", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.8 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4000 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"16000 : 8000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0018 : 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1000 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"300", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.6 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"28000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"80", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.012 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.054 : 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.81 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"90", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.27 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.09", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.048", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00054 : 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.09", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 : 100 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.049", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.001 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0004 : 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.018", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.008 : 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.007 : 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.35 : 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"30000 : 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 : 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"100 : 100 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 600 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"18000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 600 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36000 : 6000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.048 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.35 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.05", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.016 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.004", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3.2 : 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"800", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 : 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"15000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"400 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.008 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.048", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140 : 20 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.021", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"600 * 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.56", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.54", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.014", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.21 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.5 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.008 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0004 : 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.72 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.24 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 600 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"42", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500000 : 1000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"500", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.025", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7.2 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"160", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160 : 40 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"160 : 40 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.006 : 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"18 : 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"20", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.28", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2400 : 300 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00027 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.009 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.063", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"250 : 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.05", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.063 : 0.007 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"320", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.01 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3.6 : 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 : 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2700", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.2 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.2 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.018", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.012 : 0.004 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4.2 : 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 0.7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"90", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.2 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.1 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"350 : 50 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0063 : 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.09", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.6 * 0.003 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0018", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.012 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56 : 8000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 50 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"400", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.14 : 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"45000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.18 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.015 : 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.48 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.15", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.001 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.007", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"12000 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.12 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.3 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.0003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.081", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.2 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200 : 2000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.12", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"10 * 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.06", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"35 : 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.005", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.032", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3.5 : 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"450 : 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"90", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.2 : 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.06 : 0.02 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 * 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"25", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.54", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 8000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"64000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.048 : 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.035", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"56000 : 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0004 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.001", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.81", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"36000 : 6000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 * 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.01", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.0024 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.03", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.49 : 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"250 : 5000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.05", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.035 : 0.005 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.56 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"27000 : 3000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.032 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 40 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"40", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.006", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"20 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"10", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"8 * 40 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"320", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.004 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.036", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.049 : 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.02 * 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.32 : 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.9 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"500 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.72", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.24 : 80 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.4 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 700 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2100", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.07 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.42", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.16", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.064 : 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.05 * 5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.25", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 : 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"210 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"30", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"42000 : 7000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"400 * 8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3200", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.018 : 0.002 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00016 : 0.08 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.002", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.08 : 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3 * 0.008 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.024", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2 * 800 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1600", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2.4 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.005 : 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.056 : 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.008", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.54", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.2 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.07 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.35", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"40 * 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3.6", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.25 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.03 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"200 * 900 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"180000", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.072 : 0.009 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.09", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.09 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.6 : 0.8 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.15 : 0.03 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.012 : 0.006 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.003 * 3 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.15 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1 * 0.4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.8 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"4.8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"80 * 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"160", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"400 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3600", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 * 7 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.014", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"70 * 6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"420", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.18 : 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.02", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"7 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"6.3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.6 : 200 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.003", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.4 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.7", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"140 : 2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"70", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.09 : 0.01 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"9", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.36", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.00054 : 0.06 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4 * 0.5 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"90 * 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"360", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"9 * 0.001 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.009", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 * 9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.018", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"12000 : 6000 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"2", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.04 : 0.04 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"1", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"2100 : 700 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"5 * 0.1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"4000 : 800 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"6 * 0.9 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"5.4", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1.6 : 0.2 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"8", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"3200 : 4 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"800", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.002 : 0.05 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.04", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"1500 : 500 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"3", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"0.7 * 0.6 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"0.42", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
{"question":"60 : 1 = ?", "answers" : [{"value":"60", "hint" : "Ответ?"}]}
